commun.it 2019-09-22

# Privacy Policy

**All terms in capital letters not otherwise defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the GR8PPL's Terms of Use as they appear in the Website. This Privacy Policy is hereby attached by reference to the ToU, and serves as an integral part thereof.**

Great People Ltd. (" **GR8PPL** ") respects your right to privacy. Please read below to understand more about our privacy policy. This Privacy Policy applies to the Website and Services (as define at TOU) granted therein, and governs Data collection and usage thereof. By using our Website and/or the Services, you may be required to provide us with certain credentials and access rights for third party websites, and you assert your consent to GR8PPL to collect and use the information included in such websites as part of the Services and for your benefit.

  1. **Acceptance** By subscribing or using Services and/or accessing, browsing, submitting information to, or other use of the Website, You signify Your assent to both this Privacy Policy and the ToU. If You do not agree to any of these terms, You may not use, and therefore immediately cease any use of, the Services and/or the Website. 

The Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, with or without notice, at the discretion of GR8PPL provided that the latest version of the Privacy Policy will be posted on the Website. Any changes made to this Privacy Policy shall be effective immediately following the posting of such changes. You hereby agree that any subsequent access to or use by You of the Services and/or the Website shall constitute Your acceptance of all the changes thereof.

  2. **Collection of Personal Information** While providing the Services, GR8PPL may collect or receive Personal Information, whether provided directly by You or obtain through the use of Your credentials through other websites to which You are subscribed (namely Twitter or Facebook (the " **Social Networks** ")). Any credentials (such as username and password) to other third party websites, shall be used by GR8PPL solely for the purpose of providing the Service and shall not be transferred to third parties by GR8PPL.  
It is acknowledged by You that in order to provide the Services, GR8PPL may require to receive certain access rights to the Social Networks and failure to provide such rights may limit or prevent the ability of GR8PPL to provide the Services.  
The information that may be extracted, stored and used by GR8PPL may include e-mail address, names, expertise in specific topics, information with respect to Your contacts and related to them, users You respect, favorite writers and etc., identifiable information, non-public information, health related information (provided that such is disclosed by You to GR8PPL or to on the Social Networks), economic information, private correspondences, personal opinions, believes, trends and manner of activities on the web, consuming features and trends of You and Your contacts and so forth.  
Any such information shall be used by GR8PPL solely for the provision of the Services according to the terms hereof and those set forth in the ToU, and not for any other purpose without your prior consent.

Some of the information we collect, receive, use and store about you may include Personal data and/or Sensitive Personal Data as defined in **the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679**. By using the services, providing us your credentials and by accepting these Privacy Policy and the TOU, you hereby give your explicit consent to collect, use, store and transfer this Personal data or the Sensitive Personal Data all under this Privacy Policy and the TOU terms. As for the Sensitive Personal Data, we will not utilize this data unless we have your consent.Your consent may be given in orally, written or by implied (i.e. by enable our system to push this data, by made it pubic etc.)

Such information may also include information and data about Your computer hardware and software and the use thereof, that is automatically collected by GR8PPL during the use of the Website and the Services. This information can include, without limitation, Your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Website addresses.

The information as described above is used by GR8PPL for provision of the Service, to maintain quality of the Service, and for general statistics regarding use of the Website and the Service and use habits of the Website's and Service's users. 

  3. **Use of Personal Information** GR8PPL collects, stores and uses Personal Information for the provision of the Services. If, upon subscription to the Service, You've confirmed your assent to receive promotional and other commercial information by GR8PPL, then GR8PPL shall be entitled to use certain aspects of the Personal Information for promotional purposes, such as to offer You additional products or services. Under such authorization, GR8PPL shall not divulge such Personal Information to third parties.

If You consented to this, GR8PPL may contact You, from time to time, on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to You. In those cases, Your Personal Information and contact details shall not be transferred to such third parties.

GR8PPL keeps track of the Website in general, and of its users' visits of the Website in particular, in order to determine popularity of certain features, functionality of the Website and for other purposes, including commercial purposes. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the Website to users whose behavior indicates that they are more interested in a particular subject area.

You also acknowledge that GR8PLL may also track Your use of the Service for statistical purposes or to determine the popularity of certain features of the Services in order to improve the quality of Service.

**Data Retention, Archives** : In the interests of the customer, we retain and archive Personal data as long as it necessary to obtain our services, meet with contractual obligations, laws and regulations and subject to our retention policies and this Privacy Policy. Any related data transection is securely controlled by different means of cyber security methods.

**Accessing, Updating, Correcting , Deleting, restriction of processing, lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority rights under the the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the GDPR) -**

    * If the GDPR is applicable to you, you may have the right to request access to some of your Personal Data being stored by us. You can also ask to correct, update or delete any inaccurate Personal Data that we process about you. All subject to our policies and the applicable laws and regulations.
    * **How to exercise these rights** : Our Services enable you to view, edit, or delete your data online by your sole decision. GR8PPL will not have any liability when using these functions and you hereby obligate to use them according the law and regulations. If you cannot access certain personal data directly through our Services, you can always contact us by email: support@commun.it We will respond to requests to access or delete your personal data within 30 days.
    * We may retain your Personal Data for a period is permitted or required under applicable laws. Even if you delete your Personal Data it may persist on backup or archival media for an additional period of time due to technical issues or for legal, tax or regulatory reasons or for legitimate and lawful business purposes.
    * You may have the right to restriction of processing if one of the following apply:  

      * The accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject;
      * The processing is unlawful, and the data subject opposes the erasure of the personal data, and requests the restriction of their use instead;
      * Your service provider no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of the original processing, but the data is required by the data subject for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims;
      * The data subject has objected to processing pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of your service provider override those of the data subject.
      * If you wish to object the processing, you can delete your account.
    * You may have the right to lodge complaint with a supervisory authority. However, prior doing so, you welcome to contact us by email to support@commun.it in order to solve the issue for the benefit of all parties. Our supervisory authority is the Israeli Data Protection authority.
**Transfer/Share/Disclose Data** : We may share your Personal Data with our partners, affiliates, contractors, our service providers who process Personal Data on behalf of us to perform certain business-related functions. we may provide them with information, including Personal Data, in connection with their performance of such functions. While we do so we make sure that they will be bound to maintain that Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may need to **share some personal data among our development and customer service team**. For example, to provide customer service and support or assist in protecting and securing our systems and services our development and customer service team may have access to personal data. In such cases, our personnel must abide by our data privacy and security requirements and policy and are not allowed to use personal data for any other purpose. By using the Website or services and/or accepting this Privacy policy, you are hereby agree and give permission to us to do so.

Notwithstanding the abovementioned, GR8PPL will disclose Your Data, as provided via the Website or the Services, to third parties, without prior notice, only if: (a) GR8PPL is required to do so by law, or if (b) GR8PPL believes in good faith that such action is necessary to conform or comply with the provisions of any law or with legal proceedings, to protect the rights or property of GR8PPL and/or to protect the personal safety of users of GR8PPL or the public.

**In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets**. You acknowledge and agree that any successor to or acquirer of the Company (or its assets) will continue to have the right to use your Personal Data and other information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

  4. **Use of Cookies** The Website uses "Cookies" (whether of GR8PPL or of third parties) to help you personalize Your online experience. A Cookie is a text file that is placed on Your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to Your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to You, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the Cookie to You.

One of the primary purposes of Cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save You time. The purpose of a Cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. This simplifies the process of recording Your personal information, such as IP addresses, username and so on. When You return to the Website, the information You previously provided can be retrieved, so You can easily use the Website features that You customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline Cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but You can usually modify Your browser setting to decline Cookies if You prefer. If You choose to decline Cookies, You may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the services provided in the Website or other web sites You visit.

**Our Cookies Policy:**

We use cookies to let us know when you visit our websites, how you interact with us, to enrich your user experience, and to customize your relationship with us, including providing you with more relevant advertising. This includes:

**Essential Website Cookies** \- These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our websites or services and to use some of its features, such as access to secure areas. Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the websites or services, you cannot refuse them without impacting how our websites or services function. You can block or delete them by changing your browser settings.

**Performance and Functionality Cookies** \- These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our websites and services but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality may become unavailable

**Analytics and Customization Cookies** \- These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our websites and application for you in order to enhance your experience.

**Advertising (Targeting) Cookies** \- These cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you and your interests. They also perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests.

**Other tracking technologies** \- We may use other, similar technologies from time to time, like,pixels and other tracking technologies. These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enable us to recognise when someone has visited our Websites etc. This allows us, for example, to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within our Websites to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to our Websites from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, to serve targeted advertisements to you and others like you, to improve site performance, and to measure the success of marketing campaigns. While you may not have the ability to specifically reject or disable these tracking technologies, in many instances, these technologies are reliant on cookies to function properly; accordingly, in those instances, declining cookies will impair functioning of these technologies. You can control cookies by setting or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies or you can use the “Do Not Track” or “DNT” feature if available at your internet browser.

**How We Store Your Personal Information, transfer your data to 3rd parties and to non EEA countries**. As Global service providers company, we may use third parties services which located outside the EU or European Economic Area (EEA). Therefore, Personal data may be transfer stored and processed in countries outside the EU or the EEA. Such transfer to third countries may include countries that is not ensures adequate level of data protection laws as required by EU privacy laws.

We try to work with Suppliers which enables GDPR compliance but due to the nature of our business we can't guarantee that. Our servers located at USA, Limestone, server provider Company, and we backup the Information at Amazon US. AWS and Limestone are certified under the EU-US Privacy Shiled (For more information see: https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/eu-us-privacy-shield-faq/ ).

We also try to implement high level of information security technics & technical measures and/or third parties contractual obligations to maintain their Information security level adequate to our level. 

  5. **Security of Personal Information** GR8PPL reasonably secures the Personal Information extracted and stored from, together with the credentials provided by You, against unauthorized access, use or disclosure, and keeps such information on computer servers in a standard controlled and secured environment. The GR8PPL's data bases on which Your Data (and Personal Information therein) are reserved, are reasonably secured and programmed for protection from exposure and unauthorized use of such Data and/or Personal Information.
  6. **Changes to this Privacy Policy** GR8PPL may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, by placement of an updated Privacy Policy in the Website. GR8PPL encourages You to periodically review this Privacy Policy from time to time, so to be informed of the subject matters hereof.
  7. **Miscellaneous** This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data that you provide to other thierd party through the Website or Services or through any other means.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Website and Services. It is not applying to third party’s websites or services which their links may be contain in the Website or Services. The links from the Website or Services do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed the third-party websites or services. We suggest contacting these third party directly for information on their privacy policies.

**Children** : Our services does not intend to minors (under the age of 18) or children (under the age of 13). We do not knowingly receive Personal Data from minors or children. If you are a minor or a child or collect Personal data from minors or children please do not submit any Personal Data through the Website and Services without the minor/child’s parental/custodian’s approval. If you have reason to believe that a minor or a child has provided Personal Data to us through the Website or Services without its parental/custodian’s approval, you required to notify us by email to support@commun.it , and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Israel, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Any claim or dispute between You and GR8PPL that arises in whole or in part from the Website and/or in connection with the use thereof, shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Tel Aviv – Jaffa, Israel
